Preliminary Inventory to the Friedrich Katz Collection, 1919-1945
Hoover Institution Archives
- IV: The Jewish question (Die Judenfrage), 1867-1944 (Box 43)
  - History (Geschichte)
    - Germany (Deutschland)
      - Jewish parties (Judenparteien)
        - Social democrats (Sozialdemokraten), 1919-1924
    - Africa (Afrika)
      - Jews in Tunis (Die Juden in Tunis), 1925 (Folder 44: 2)
      - Africa (Afrika), n.d.
      - Morocco (Marokko), n.d.
    - United States of America (Amerika)
      - North America (Nordamerika), 1923-1925 (Folder 44: 3)
      - South America (Südamerika), n.d.
  - History and nature of Judaism (Geschichte und Wesen des Judentums)
    - General – History (Allgemeines - nur Geschichte), 1922-1926 (Folder 44: 4)
    - The spread of Jews all over the world (Die Ausbreitung der Juden über die Erde), n.d.
    - Jewish laws (Jüdische Gesetze), n.d.
    - Jewish sects (Juden-Sekten), n.d.
    - The character of Judaism (Zum Wesen des Judentums), 1903-1925
    - Laws for and against Jews (Gesetze betreffend und gegen die Juden)
    - Jews and physical work (Die Juden und die körperliche Arbeit), 1894
    - Conventions and customs (Sitten und Gebräuche), 1903-1923 (Folder 44: 5)
    - Christianity and Judaism (Christentum und Judentum), 1906-1923
    - Jews in the evangelical and catholic clergy (Judenabkömmlinge in der evangelischen und katholischen Geistlichkeit)
    - Jews and Jesuits (Juden und Jesuiten)
    - Jewish frivolity (Jüdische Frechheiten), 1923-1924
    - Jüdische Überhebungen, 1925
    - Jewish proletariat (Jüdisches Proletariat), n.d.
    - Jews and the term "fatherland" (Die Juden und der Begriff "Vaterland"), 1920-1923 (Folder 44: 6)
    - The Jewish part in the revolution (Die Rolle der Juden in der Revolution)
    - World war and revolution (Weltkrieg und Revolution), 1921-1924
    - Penetration and demoralization of the society by Jews (Das Eindringen in die Gesellschaft und das Zersetzen der Gesellschaft durch die Juden) (Box-folder 45: 1)
    - The era of attempting assimilation – Jewish emancipation (Die Ära der Assimilationsbestrebungen – Juden–Emanzipation)
    - The direct consequences of the achievement of equal rights for Jews (Die unmittelbaren Folgen der Erkämpfung der Gleichberechtigung der Juden)
    - Jews in national and city parliaments (Juden in Staats– und Stadtparlamenten)
    - The Jewish part in the establishment of the modern state (Der Anteil der Juden an der Begründung des modernen Staates), 1923
    - The Jewish part in the history of European colonies (Der Anteil der Juden in der Geschichte der europäischen Kolonien), 1922
    - The state of All Judaan (Der Staat Alljudaan), 1922-1926 (Folder 45: 2)
    - The Zionist congress in Vienna (Der Zionistenkongress in Wien), 1925
    - Hoböhmen
      - General (Allgemeines), 1919-1926 (Folder 45: 3)
      - Daimling, 1924-1927
      - Stresemann, 1923-1924
      - Delbrück, 1922-1925
      - Max von Baden, 1924
      - Severing, 1922-1924
    - Miscellany (Verschiedenes)
      - Pacifism (Pazifimus), 1920-1923 (Folder 45: 4)
      - International (Internationale), 1920-1923
    - Jews at the Prussian election (Juden bei der Preussenwahl), 1921
    - Jewish media (Judenpresse)
      - Miscellany (Verschiedenes), 1919-1924 (Folder 45: 5)
      - Der jüdische Zeitungspolyp von Th. Fripsch, 1922
  - Jewish leaders (Jüdische Führer)
    - Miscellany (Verschiedenes), 1924-1926 (Folder 45: 6)
    - Disraeli, n.d. (Folder 45: 7)
    - Maximilian Harden, 1922-1923
    - Rathenau, 1921-1922
  - Jews in businesses (Juden im Wirtschaftsleben), 1921-1924 (Box-folder 46: 1)
  - Jews in art and science (Juden in Kunst und Wissenschaft), 1921-1924 (Folder 46: 2)
  - Jews in military service (Juden im Heeresdienst), 1919-1922 (Folder 46: 3)
  - Jews and freemasonry (Juden und Freimaurerei), 1919-1935 (Folder 46: 4)
  - Jews as criminals (Juden als Verbrecher), 1919-1922 (Folder 46: 5)
  - Judicial sentences relating to Jews and Judaism (Urteile über Juden und Judentum)
    - Miscellany (Verschiedenes), 1919 (Folder 46: 6)
    - Bismarck, n.d.
    - Richard Wagner, n.d.
    - Nietzsche, n.d.
    - Napoleon I, n.d.
  - Statistics on Jews (Judenstatik), 1922-1927 (Box-folder 47: 1)
  - Defense against Jews (Judenabwehr), 1903-1924 (Folder 47: 2)
  - Sklareks, 1938 (Folder 47: 3)
  - Catalog of writings relating to Judaism (Verzeichnis von Schriften betreffend dem Judentum), 1914-1922 (Folder 47: 4)
  - Miscellaneous clippings (Verschiedene Zeitungsartikel über die Judenfrage), 1941-1943 (Folder 47: 5)
  - Unsorted clippings (Unsortierte Zeitungsartikel über die Judenfrage), 1941-1943 (Box-folder 48: 1-2)
  - History – Middle Ages (Geschichte – Mittelalter)
    - General (Allgemeines), n.d. (Folder 48: 3)
    - Jews in the Roman Empire since Constantine (Die Juden im römischen Weltreich seit der Zeit Konstantins), n.d.
    - Papacy and Judaism (Papsttum und Judentum)
    - Jews in the Frankish kingdom (Die Juden im fränkischen Reich), n.d.
    - Jews in Germany (Die Juden in Deutschland)
    - Jews in England (Die Juden in England)
    - Jews in France (Die Juden in Frankreich), n.d.
    - Jews in Spain/Portugal (Die Juden in Spanien/Portugal), 1922
    - Jews in Poland (Die Juden in Polen)
  - History and character of Judaism (Geschichte und Wesen des Judentums)
    - Palestine (Palästina), 1923-1926 (Folder 48: 4)
    - Zionism (4 booklets) (Zionismus) (4 Hefte), 1912-1920
  - Literature (Literatur zur Judenfrage)
    - Books and booklets (Bücher und Hefte)
      - Dubnow, Simon, Weltgeschichte des jüdischen Volkes, 1925
        - Bd. II (Folder 48: 5)
        - Bd. IX (Box-folder 49: 1)
      - Ford, Henry, Der internationale Jude, Bd. I und II, 1923 (Folder 49: 2-3)
      - Mittelstädt, Otto, Die Affaire Dreyfus, 1899 (Box-folder 50: 1)
      - Schrupp, Karla, Edouard Drumont und sein Kamf gegen das Judentum in Frankreich, 1944 (Folder 50: 2)
      - Bergel, Siegmund, Kischinew und die Lage der Juden in Russland, 1903 (Folder 50: 3)
      - Kranz, M.
        - Neu-Polen, 1915 (Folder 50: 4)
        - Polen oder Pollacken?, 1939 (Folder 50: 5)
      - Lauer, Bernhard
        - Die Juden in Österreich, 1908 (Folder 50: 6)
        - Zum polnisch-jüdischen Problem, 1915 (Box-folder 51: 1)
      - Rosenfeld, Max, Nationale Autonomie der Juden in Österreich, 1912 (Folder 51: 2)
      - Frei, Bruno, Jüdisches Elend in Wien, 1920 (Folder 51: 3)
      - Schneidewin, Max, Die jüdische Frage im deutschen Reich, 1894 (Folder 51: 4)
      - Schultze, Franz, Deutschlands Weltmachtstellung, 1915 (Folder 51: 5)
      - Naudh, H., Die Juden und der deutsche Staat, 1883 (Folder 51: 6)
      - Makower, H., Über die Gemeinde-Verhältnisse der Juden in Preussen, 1873 (Folder 51: 7)
      - Stobbe, Otto, Die Juden in Deutschland während des Mittelalters, 1902 (Folder 51: 8)
      - Weyden, Ernst, Geschichte der Juden in Köln am Rhein von den Römerzeiten bis auf die Gegenwart, 1867 (Folder 51: 9)
      - Rieger, Dr., Ein Vierteljahrhundert im Kampf um das Recht und die Zukunft der deutschen Juden, 1918 (Folder 51: 10)
      - Wohlgemuth, J., Die Richtlinien zu einem Programm für das liberale Judentum, n.d. (Folder 51: 11)
      - Suβmann, Arthur, Demokratis und Judenfrage, 1920 (Folder 51: 12)
      - Liebig, von H., Erzberger als Staatsmann und Werkzeug, 1919 (Folder 51: 13)
      - Hilmar, Karl, Die deutschen Juden im Weltkriege, 1918 (Box-folder 52: 1)
      - Armin, Otto
        - Die Juden im Heer, 1919 (Folder 52: 2)
        - Die Juden in den Kriegsgesellschaften (Folder 52: 3)
      - Deutsche Corpszeitung: Amtliche Zeitschrift des Kösener G. C. Verbandes, 1919 October (Folder 52: 4)
      - Scherbel, Simon, Jüdische Ärzte, 1905 (Folder 52: 5)
      - Eppstein, Max, Das Theater als Geschäft, 1911 (Folder 52: 6)
      - Herzl, Theodor, Zionistische Schriften, 1920 (Folder 52: 7)
      - Liebermann, A., Der Schulchan Arüch, 1912 (Box-folder 53: 1)
      - Löhr, Max, Israels Kulturentwicklung, 1911 (Folder 53: 2)
      - Baron, David, Der Hirts Israels und seine zerstreute Herde, 1911 (Folder 53: 3)
      - Monthly (Monatsschrift), Der Jude, Jahrgang I., Heft 3, 1916 Juni (Folder 53: 4)
      - Goldmann, Nachum, Von der weltkulturellen Bedeutung und Aufgabe des Judentums, 1916 (Folder 53: 5)
      - Monthly (Monatsschrift), Liberales Judentum, Jahrg. I, Heft 1, 1909 (Folder 53: 6)
      - Eiganbrodt, August, Berliner Tageblatt und Frankfurter Zeitung in ihrem Verhalten zu den nationalen Fragen, 1887-1914, 1917 (Folder 53: 7)
      - Mandl, Simon, Das Wesen des Judentums, 1904 (Folder 53: 8)
      - Kautsky, Karl, Rasse und Judentum, 1921 (Folder 53: 9)
      - Science academy for Judaism, report ("Lehranstalt für die Wissenschaft des Judentums", Bericht), 1915-1918 (Folder 53: 10)
      - Bergmann, J., Jüdische Apologetik im neutestamentischen Zeitalter, 1908 (Folder 53: 11)
      - Marr, W., Religiöse Streifzüge eines philosophischen Touristen, 1876 (Folder 53: 12)
      - Torczyner, Harry, Die Bundeslande und die Anfänge der Religion Israels, 1922 (Folder 53: 13)
      - Singer, J., Sollen die Juden Christen werden?, 1884 (Folder 53: 14)
      - Dinter, Arthur, Der Kampf um die Vollendung der Reformation, 1928 (Box-folder 54: 1)
      - Chasanowitsch, Leon und Motzkin, Leo, Die Judenfrage der Gegenwart, 1919 (Folder 54: 2)
      - Kaplun-Kogan, Wlad W., Die jüdische Wanderbewegung in der neuesten Zeit (1880-1914), 1919 (Folder 54: 3)
      - Stauf v.d. Warch, O., Die Juden im Urteil der Zeiten, 1921 (Folder 54: 4)
      - Treitschke v. Heinrich, Ein Wort über Judentum, 1881 (Folder 54: 5)
      - Gransky, K., Richard Wagner und die Juden, 1919 (Folder 54: 6)
      - Wagner, Richard, Das Judentum in der Musik, 1869 (Folder 54: 7)
      - Falb, Alfred, Luther und die Juden, 1921 (Folder 54: 8)
      - Rosenberg, Alfred, Die Protokolle der Weisen von Zion und die jüdische Weltpolitik, 1923 (Folder 54: 9)
      - Werner, F., Der Wahrheit einer Gasse! Eine Abrechnung mit dem Judentum und seinen Helfern, 1919 (Folder 54: 10)
      - Meister, Wilhelm, Judas Schuldbuch, eine deutsche Abrechnung, 1920 (Box-folder 55: 1)
      - Stille, Gustav, Der Kampf gegen das Judentum, 1892 (Folder 55: 2)
      - Seifert, H. E., Der Jude zwischen den Fronten, 1942 (Folder 55: 3)
      - Kolenscher, Rechtsverhältnisse der Juden, 1910 (Folder 55: 4)
      - Fritsch, Theodore, Antisemiten-Katechismus, 1892 (Folder 55: 5)
      - Wichtl, Friedrich, Freimaurerei und Judentum, handwritten essays (handschriftliche Aufsätze) (Folder 55: 6)
      - Custos, Dr., Freimaurer: Der Weltvampyr, 1931 (Folder 55: 7)
      - Dlugosch, Wilhelm, 1893-1938
        - Eine Volksgemeinschaft vernichtet die Freimaurerei, 1938 (Folder 55: 8)
        - Juden in Freimaurerorden und Geschichte der Freimaurerei, 2 handwritten essays (2 handschriftliche Artikel), 1893-1936 (Folder 55: 9)
      - Sombart, Werner, Zur Judenfrage, handwritten essays (handschriftliche Artikel) (Box-folder 56: 1)
      - Hest, Heinrich, Paläina: Judenstaat? England als Handlanger des Weltjudentums, 1939 (Folder 56: 2)
      - Nawratzki, Curt, Das neue jüdische Palästina, 1919 (Folder 56: 3)
      - Sokolow, Nahum, Geschichte des Zionismus, 1917 (Folder 56: 4)
      - Margulies, Heinrich, Kritik des Zionismus, 1920 (Folder 56: 5)
      - Böhm Adolf, Die zionische Bewegung, 1920 (Folder 56: 6)
      - Hedin, Sven, Jerusalem, 1918 (Folder 56: 7)
      - 1 file with 22 writings (1 Mappe mit 22 Schriften zur Judenfrage), 1869-1924 (Box-folder 57: 1)
      - 1 file with 6 writings (1 Mappe mit 6 Schriften zur Judenfrage), 1907-1915 (Folder 57: 2)
- V: World War II (Der 2. Weltkrieg), 1941-1945
  - Miscellany from and about the war (Vermischtes aus und über den Krieg), 1941-1943 (Folder 57: 3)
  - The war – overall view (Der Krieg – Gesamtdarstellungen), 1941-1942 (Folder 57: 4)
  - Maps of different theaters of war (Karten der verschiedenen Kriegsschauplätze), 1940-1944 (Box-folder 58: 1)
  - The eastern front (Die zweite Front) (Invasion), 1942-1944 (Folder 58: 2)
  - Atlantikwall, 1942-1944 (Folder 58: 3)
  - Oberkommando der Wehrmacht – reports (Berichte)
    - Poland campaign (Polenfeldzug), 1939 August 31 - Oktober 10 (Folder 58: 4)
    - Static warfare in the west (Stellungskampf im Westen), 1939 October 18 - 1940 April 8 (Box-folder 59: 1)
    - The occupation of Denmark and Norway (Besetzung von Dänemark und Norwegen), 1940 April 9 - May 9 (Folder 59: 2)
    - The abolition of France (Die Niederwerfung Frankreichs), 1940 May 10 - June 25 (Folder 59: 3)
    - War against England (Der Krieg gegen England), 1940 June 26 - September 15 (Folder 59: 4)
    - War against England (Der Krieg gegen England), 1941 September 16 - January 10 (Box-folder 60: 1)
    - German aid for Italy (Deutsche Hilfe für Italien), 1941 January 10 - April 5 (Folder 60: 2)
    - The Balkan campaign (Der Balkanfeldzug), 1941 April 16 - June 2
      - Crete (Kreta) (Folder 60: 3)
      - Revolt of Iraq (Erhebung des Irak)
    - Official communiqués (Heeresberichte) (Box 61)
      - First term (1. Halbjahr), 1943 (Folder 61: 1)
      - Second term (2. Halbjahr), 1943 (Folder 61: 2)
      - 1945 January 1 - March 31 (Folder 61: 3)
  - European theaters of war (Europäische Kriegsschauplätze) (Box 62)
    - General – history, geography and economy (Allgemeines - Geschichte, Geografie und Wirtschaft), 1940-1944 (Folder 62: 1-2)
    - The campaign (Der Feldzug) (Box 63)
      - in the west (im Westen), 1941-1942 (Folder 63: 1)
      - in Norway (in Norwegen), 1942 (Folder 63: 2)
    - The Balkan campaign and Crete (Der Balkanfeldzug und Kreta), 1942 (Folder 63: 3)
    - The war in Italy (Der Krieg in Italien), 1943-1944 (Folder 63: 4)
    - The war in the East (Der Krieg im Osten)
      - Single writings (Einzelschriften), 1942-1943 (Folder 63: 5)
      - 1941 unsorted (unsortiert), 1941-1942 (Folder 63: 6)
      - First campaign (1. Feldzug), 1941 (Folder 63: 7)
      - Winter, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 64: 1)
      - 1942 May – June (Folder 64: 2)
      - 1942 July (Box-folder 65: 1-2)
      - 1942 August - September (Folder 65: 3-4)
      - 1942 October - December (Box-folder 66: 1-2)
      - 1943 January (Folder 66: 3-4)
      - 1943 February (Box-folder 67: 1)
      - 1943 March (Folder 67: 2)
      - 1943 April (Folder 67: 3)
      - 1943 May - June (Folder 67: 4)
      - 1943 July (Folder 67: 5)
      - 1943 August (Box-folder 68: 1)
      - 1943 September - October (Folder 68: 2)
      - 1943 November - December (Folder 68: 3)
      - 1944 January - March (Folder 68: 4)
      - 1944 April - June (Folder 68: 5)
  - American-English aggression against French Africa (Amerikanisch-Englischer Angriff auf Französisch Afrika)
    - Theaters of war (Die Kriegsschauplätze) (Folder 68: 6)
      - History, geography, economy, maps (Geschichte, Geographie, Wirtschaft, Karte), 1942-1943 (Folder 68: 6)
      - 1942 October 11 - November 30 (Box-folder 69: 1-2)
      - 1942 December 1 - 1943 March 31 (Folder 69: 3-4)
  - War in Africa (Afrika-Krieg) (Box 70)
    - 1942 January 2 – June 30 (Folder 70: 1-2)
    - 1941-1943, with maps (mit Kartenmaterial) (Box-folder 71: 1-2)
    - 1942 July 1 – December 31 (Folder 71: 3-4)
    - 1943 January 1 – June 5 (Box-folder 72: 1-3)
  - Japan's campaign in greater East Asia (Japans Kampf um Grossostasien) (Box 73)
    - War reports (Kriegsberichte)
      - 1942 January 1 – May 31 (Folder 73: 1-2)
      - 1942 June 1 – December 31 (Folder 73: 3-4)
      - 1943 (Box-folder 74: 1-3)
      - 1944 (Box-folder 75: 1-2)
    - Greater East Asia – miscellany (Grossostasien – Verschiedenes)
      - 1943 (Folder 75: 3)
      - 1944 (Box-folder 76: 1-2)
      - 1944 (Box-folder 77: 1-4)
    - India (Indien), 1942-1944 (Box-folder 78: 1-2)
    - Tibet, Sinkiang, Mentschiang, Mongolei, Mandschukuo, 1939-1944 (Folder 78: 3-4)
    - Tschunking–China, 1941-1944 (Box-folder 79: 1-2)
    - Nanking–China, 1937-1944 (Folder 79: 3)
    - Burma, Thailand, Indochina (Französisch-Indochina), 1941-1944 (Box-folder 80: 1-2)
    - The Malayan area: Malaya, Philippines, Sumatra, Java, Borneo, Celebes, New Guinea, Solomon Islands, miscellany, and the history of the Dutch colonial empire (Der malaische Raum: Malaia, Philippinen, Sumatra, Java, Borneo, Celebes, Neu Guinea, Salomon-Inseln, Vermischtes, und zur Geschichte des niederländischen Kolonialreiches), 1941-1943 (Box-folder 81: 1-2)
    - The East Asian area and Japan (Der ostasiatische Grossraum und Japan), 1942-1944 (Folder 81: 3-4)
    - Battle on Madagascar (Der Kampf um Madagaskar), 1942 May - December (Box-folder 82: 1)
    - Australia, unsorted articles (Australien) (unsortierte Artikel), 1928-1945 (Folder 82: 2-3)
    - Naval warfare (Seekrieg), 1941-1942 (Box-folder 83: 1-2)
    - Naval warfare (Seekrieg), 1943 – aerial warfare (Luftkrieg), 1942-1943 (Folder 83: 3-4)
    - Aerial and naval warfare (unsorted articles) (Luft- und Seekrieg) (unsortierte Artikel), 1942-1944 (Box-folder 84: 1-3)
  - Special files (Sondermappen) (Box 85)
    - Arms (Waffen)
      - Army (Heer), 1941-1943 (Folder 85: 1)
      - Marine, 1941-1942 (Folder 85: 2)
      - Air force (Luftwaffe), 1942 (Folder 85: 3)
      - Railroad and cars (Eisenbahn und Auto), 1941-1943 (Folder 85: 4)
      - Organisation Todt (OT); Reichsarbeitsdienst (RAD), 1941-1942 (Folder 85: 5)
      - Miscellany (Vermischtes), 1941-1943 (Folder 85: 6)
      - Toxic gas (Giftgas), 1942-1944 (Folder 85: 7)
    - General Staff (Generalstab), 1942 (Folder 85: 8)
    - Tactics (Taktik), 1942-1943 (Folder 85: 9)
    - Strategy (Strategie), 1941-1943 (Folder 85: 10)
    - Notation of campaigns and combats (Bezeichnung der Schlachten und Gefechte), 1942-1943 (Folder 85: 11)
    - Women in war (Frauen im Kriege), 1942-1943 (Folder 85: 12)
    - War targets (Kriegsziele), 1942-1943 (Folder 85: 13)
    - Freedom drivel (Friedensgefasel), 1941-1942 (Folder 85: 14)
    - Aggressive sadism (Feindlicher Sadismus), 1942-1943 (Folder 85: 15)
    - European volunteers against Soviet Russia (Europäische Freiwillige gegen Sowjetrussland), 1942 (Folder 85: 16)
    - General Wlassow – Russians against Soviets (Russen gegen Sowjets), 1941-1943 (Folder 85: 17)
    - Aggressive landfalls (Feindliche Landungsversuche), 1942 (Folder 85: 18)
    - Dieppe, 1942 August 19 (Box-folder 86: 1)
    - Military science – war history to 1914 (Militärwissenschaften - Kriegsgeschichte bis 1914), 1932-1942 (Folder 86: 2-3)
    - World war (Weltkrieg) (Box 87)
      - 1914-1942 (Folder 87: 1-3)
      - 1914-1918 (miscellany, eastern and other theaters of war, marine, espionage) (Vermischtes, Östliche und Nebenkriegsschauplätze, Marine, Spionage), 1932-1938 (Box-folder 88: 1-3)
    - European theaters of war (Europäische Kriegsschauplätze) (Box 89)
      - Battle of Sicily (Der Kampf um Sizilien) (Folder 89: 1-4)
        - Theaters of war and maps (Kriegsschauplätze und Karten), 1943
        - Lampedusa und Pantelleria, 1943
        - Prehistory (Vorgeschichte), 1943
        - Battle of Sicily (Der Kampf um Sizilien), 1943 July 10 – August 17
        - Final consideration (Abschliessende Betrachtungen), 1943
    - Japan's campaign in greater East Asia, political prehistory of the war (Japans Kampf um Grossostasien, zur politischen Vorgeschichte des Krieges) (Box 90)
      - Theaters of war (Kriegschauplätze) (Folder 90: 1)
      - 1941 Dezember (Folder 90: 2)
    - Japan (Box 91)
      - Characteristics about the Japanese world (Charakteristisches der japanischen Welt), 1942-1943 (Folder 91: 1)
      - Politics and economy (Japans Politik und Wirtschaft), 1941-1944 (Folder 91: 2)
      - The Japanese Wehrmacht (Die japanische Wehrmacht), 1932-1943 (Folder 91: 3-4)
      - History (Geschichte), 1942-1943
      - Culture (Kultur), 1942-1943
- VI: Unsorted newspapers (Unsortierte Zeitungen) ((Völkischer Beobachter, Deutsche Allgemeine Zeitung, u.a.), 1918-1944 (Box 92)
  - Partially sorted
    - Greater East Asia, Croatia and Southeast Europe, South America(Gross Ostasien, Kroatien und Südosteuropa, Südamerika), 1943 November -Dezember (Folder 92: 1)
    - War history (Kriegsgeschichte), 1941 September – 1943 September (Folder 92: 2)
    - Das neue Europa, 1941 May – 1943 December (Folder 92: 3)
    - Southeast (Südosten), 1940 December – 1943 July (Folder 92: 4)
    - Völkischer Beobachter, 1940 June – 1943 May (Folder 92: 5)
    - War in the East (Der Krieg im Osten), 1942 March – 1943 November (Folder 92: 6)
  - Unsorted
    - 1918 April – 1925 December (Folder 92: 7)
    - 1933 December – 1943 December (Box-folder 93: 1)
    - 1937 July – 1944 April (Folder 93: 2)
    - 1940 June – 1943 April (Folder 93: 3)
    - 1941 August – 1943 December (Folder 93: 4)
    - 1941 September – 1943 November (Folder 93: 5)
    - 1941 October – 1944 January (Box-folder 94: 1-2)
    - 1941 November – 1943 December (Folder 94: 3-4)
    - 1942 September – December (Folder 94: 5)
    - 1944 August 31 (Folder 94: 6)
    - 1944 September 1-15 (Box-folder 95: 1-2)
- VII. Closed Material. Unstable original documents. Use copies of all unstable originals are available in place of the originals (Box-folder 96: 1-3)